Oliver Wolcott, Jr. Papers
Connecticut Historical Society
- I. Wolcott's Bound Volumes
  - Vol. 16. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January - June, 1802; (18 items) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 16. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., July - December, 1802; (17 items) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 16. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January - August, 1803; (12 items) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 16. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr. A List of the Several State Banks established in the United States, with their Capitals, Dividends, 1798., 1798; September - December, 1803; (19 items) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Vol.17. Letters to Oliver Wolcott from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1783 - 1789; (4 items) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 17. Letters to Oliver Wolcott and Laura Wolcott from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., Chauncey Goodrich., 1789 - 1790; (16 items) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 17. Letters to Oliver Wolcott from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1791; (11 items) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 17. Letters to Oliver Wolcott from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1792; (6 items) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 17. Letters to Oliver Wolcott and Laura Wolcott (Dec. 21, 1789) from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1793 - January 2, 1794; (18 items) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 17. Letters to Oliver Wolcott from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1794; (12 items) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 17. Letters to Oliver Wolcott from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1795; (7 items) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 17. Letters to Oliver Wolcott from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1796; (11 items) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 17. Letters to Oliver Wolcott from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1797; (5 items) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 17. Letters to Oliver Wolcott from Oliver Ellsworth., 1783; (4 items) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 17. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott and Oliver Ellsworth., 1789; (2 items) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 17. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott and Oliver Ellsworth., 1794; (2 items) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Vol. 17. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott and Oliver Ellsworth and Jonathan Trumbull., 1796; (8 items) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Vol. 17. Letters to Oliver Wolcott from Uriah Tracy, 1797; (5 items) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Vol. 18. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. from George Cabot., 1793 - 1796; (11 items) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 18. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. from George Cabot., 1797; (14 items) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 18. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. from George Cabot., 1798; (8 items) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 18. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. from George Cabot., 1799; (7 items) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 18. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. from George Cabot., 1800; (12 items) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 18. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. from George Cabot., 1801 - 1809; (16 items) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 18. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. from Fisher Ames., 1795 - 1797; (10 items) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 18. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. from Fisher Ames., 1798 - 1800; (13 items) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 18. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. from Fisher Ames., 1801 - 1802; (4 items) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 19. Letters and supporting documents concerning the Whiskey Rebellion., October - December, 1792; (15 items) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 19. Letters from John Nevill concerning the Whiskey Rebellion., 1793; (3 items) (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 19. Letters and supporting documents concerning the Whiskey Rebellion., 1794; (12 items) (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 19. Letters and supporting documents concerning the Whiskey Rebellion., 1794; (16 items) (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 19. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. during the Yellow Fever epidemic in Philadelphia., September, 1793; (14 items) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 19. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. during the Yellow Fever epidemic in Philadelphia., October, 1793; (16 items) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 19. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. during the Yellow Fever epidemic in Philadelphia., October, 1793; (16 items) (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 19. Letters and supporting documents to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. during the Yellow Fever epidemic in Philadelphia., 1789 - 1793; (9 items) (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 20. List of correspondents in Vol. 20. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January - June, 1804; (18 items) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 20. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., July - December 1804; (14 items) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 20. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January - May, 1805; (19 items) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 20. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. from Josiah Quincy, Benjamin Tallmadge, and Joseph Hopkinson., June - December, 1805; (13 items) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 20. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January - February, 1806; (20 items) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 20. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. from Uriah Tracy, Josiah Quincy, Alexander Collins, Timothy Pickering, Nathaniel Pendleton, and Tapping Reeve., March, 1806; (12 items) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 20. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., April - June, 1806; (11 items) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 20. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., July - December, 1806; (14 items) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 20. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1807; (20 items) (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 21. Drafts of letters to Alexander Hamilton from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1777 - 1796; (10 items) (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 21. Plan for establishing departments of the Bank of the United States., 1791; (1 items) (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 21. Drafts of letters to Alexander Hamilton, Rufus King, and Fisher Ames from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1797 - 1798; (16 items) (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 21. Letters to Fisher Ames from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1799 - 1803; (3 items) (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 21. Letters to George Cabot from Oliver Wolcott, Jr.; Wolcott's notes on Burr and Jefferson; List of Judges of the Supreme Court in Connecticut from the year 1750 to 1801., 1797 - 1801; (4 items) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 21. Oliver Wolcott, Jr.'s notes concerning the judiciary laws in the United States., [between 1763 - 1803]; (5 items) (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 21. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr.; Wolcott's notes on political events., 1795 - 1804; (8 items) (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 21. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., Edmund Randolph and William Ellery concerning the Fauchet affair; Wolcott's notes on the Fauchet affair., 1794 - 1796; (9 items) (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 21. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr; Memorial.. .to Congress by the Circuit Judges, Dec. 1802., (5 items) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 21. Drafts of letters from Oliver Wolcott, Jr. Material concerning Circuit Courts and the Judiciary Act., 1790 - 1802; (8 items) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 21. Rough draft of a letter (30 pages) to Fisher Ames from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January 24, 1803; (1 items) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 21. Letters and supporting documents to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1798 - 1802; (8 items) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 21. Drafts of Oliver Wolcott, Jr.'s writings. Essay for Newspaper on the subject of Mr. Jefferson's negotiations with Barbary Powers; The Weekly Inspector Fessenden Papers; Notice to Mandarins; Memorandum, 1808; (6 items) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 21. Letters with supporting documents to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1807 - 1808; (7 items) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 21. Copy of Vol. 21, number 28. Oliver Wolcott, Jr.'s notes concerning the judiciary laws in the United States., [between 1763 - 1803]; (1 item) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 22. Copies of letters from Timothy Pickering delivered to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. by John Marshall in January, 1807., 1797; (4 items) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 22. Copies of letters from Timothy Pickering; remarks on the draught of a bill to regulate interior commerce with the subjects of Great Britain...; Remarks on the 3rd Article of the Treaty of Amity, Commerce, and Navigation between the U. S. and Great Britain; letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1798 - 1808; (11 items) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 22. Copies of letters from Timothy Pickering; letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1798; (8 items) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 22. Copies of letters from Timothy Pickering., 1798 - 1799; (14 items) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 22. Copies of letters from Timothy Pickering; Instructions to John Quincy Adams Esquire... to his Majesty the King of Prussia., 1798 - 1799; (11 items) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 22. Copies of letters from Timothy Pickering; letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1800 - 1808; (12 items) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 22. Letters and supporting documents to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. from John Steele and Edward Jones., 1796 - 1798; (13 items) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 22. Letters and supporting documents to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1797 - 1801; (10 items) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 22. Notes on the Proposals of Major Graham of NC for casting Cannon, Shells, etc; letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr. and John Steele., 1795 - 1802; (14 items) (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 22. Letters and drafts of letters from Alexander Hamilton., 1794; (4 items) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 22. Letters and drafts of letters from Alexander Hamilton., 1793; (22 items) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 22. Letter to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. from Elizabeth Hamilton with a draft of Wolcott's response., 1819; (2 items) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 23. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1812 - 1814; (9 items) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 23. Letters and supporting documents to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1814 -1816; (11 items) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 23. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr.; Report of the Commissioners superintending the construction of a Steam Vessel of War to the Secretary of the Navy., 1813; (13 items) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 23. Letters with supporting documents to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr. and Rufus King., 1814; (15 items) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 23. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr. and Rufus King., 1814 - 1815; (5 items) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 23. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. from Rufus King., 1815 - 1816; (10 items) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 23. Letters and supporting documents to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1814; (11 items) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 23. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. from Elias Boudinot and Decius Wadsworth., 1813 - 1815; (9 items) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 23. Letters and supporting documents to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1814; (9 items) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 23. Socratic interrogations on the subject of Gouverneur Morris' toast and oration on the deliverance of Europe, July, 1814; letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1813 - 1814; (5 items) (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 23. Letters and supporting documents to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1813 - 1815; (16 items) (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 23. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1814 - 1815; (14 items) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 23. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr.; The Memorial of the Merchants of the City of New York; resolutions of Federal Republicans (1806)., 1806; 1814 - 1815; (7 items) (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 23. Copy of letter from Oliver Wolcott to Caleb Lownes which was published in the "Harmony Society Documentary History.", Oct. 10, 1814; (1 items) (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 24. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1808; (15 items) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 24. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. (one in French); extracts of letters; related print material., 1806 - 1811; (22 items) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 24. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1810 - 1812; (3 items) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 24. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1812 - 1813; (14 items) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 24. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1814; (5 items) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 24. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1812 - 1814; (7 items) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 24. Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1808 - 1816; (13 items) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 25. A collection of papers relating to the Frontier Territories of the United States collected principally in the year 1796. Letters and documents concerning the Atlantic Provinces region of Canada., 1789 - 1790; (6 items) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 25. Letters and supporting documents concerning trade with Canada; Order of the Governor in Council for the 7th July 1796, for the Regulation of Commerce, between This Province [Quebec] and the United States of America., 1795 - 1796; (15 items) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 25. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr.; Order of the Governor in Council, of the 7th July 1796, for the Regulation of Commerce, between this Province [Quebec] and the United States of America., (8 items) (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 25. Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. concerning relations with Canada and New Orleans., 1796 - 1797; (6 items) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 25. Letters and supporting Treasury Department documents concerning customs duties., 1790 - 1800; (13 items) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 26. Drafts of letters from the Comptroller's Office., August, 1791; (7 items) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 26. Drafts of letters from the Comptroller's Office., September, 1791; (9 items) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 26. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., October, 1791; (7 items) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 26. Drafts of letters from the Comptroller's Office., November - December, 1791; (13 items) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 26. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., October - November, 1791; (24 items) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 26. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., October, 1791; (8 items) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 26. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., January, 1792; (6 items) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 26. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., February - March, 1792; (12 items) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 26. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., April - May, 1792; (12 items) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 26. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., June, 1792; (13 items) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 26. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., July - August, 1792; (8 items) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 26. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., October - November, 1792; (13 items) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 26. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., November - December, 1792; (11 items) (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 26. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., January - February, 1793; (6 items) (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 26. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., March - April 1793; (13 items) (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 26. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., May - June, 1793; (8 items) (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 26. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., August, 1793; (2 items) (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 27. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., August, 1793; (7 items) (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Vol. 27. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., September - October, 1793; (16 items) (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Vol. 27. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office; Explanations and Forms of Official Documents in Relation to the Acts concerning the Registering, Recording, Enrolling and Licensing Ships and Vessels (Dec. 1793)., November - December, 1793; (13 items) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 27. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., January, 1794; (15 items) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 27. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., February - March, 1794; (10 items) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 27. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., April, 1794; (17 items) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 27. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., May, 1794; (17 items) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 27. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., June, 1794; (28 items) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 27. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., July, 1794; (20 items) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 28. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., August, 1794; (16 items) (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 28. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., September, 1794; (14 items) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 28. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., October, 1794; (19 items) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 28. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., October, 1794; (9 items) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 28. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., November, 1794; (13 items) (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 28. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., December, 1794; (15 items) (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 28. Drafts of letters from Comptroller's Office., 1794; (11 items) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 29. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., January, 1795; (12 items) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 29. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., January, 1795; (10 items) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 29. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., January, 1795; (20 items) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 29. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., February, 1795; (8 items) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 29. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., February, 1795; (14 items) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 29. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., March 1 - 15, 1795; (15 items) (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 29. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., March 16 - 31, 1795; (17 items) (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 29. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., April, 1795; (22 items) (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 29. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., May, 1795; (19 items) (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 30. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., June, 1795; (18 items) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 30. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., July, 1795; (21 items) (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 30. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., July, 1795; (16 items) (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 30. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., August, 1795; (13 items) (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 30. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., September, 1795; (15 items) (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 30. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., October, 1795; (15 items) (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 30. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., March - December, 1795; (19 items) (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 31. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., January, 1796; (11 items) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 31. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., February, 1796; (9 items) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 31. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., March - April, 1796; (13 items) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 31. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., May, 1796; (4 items) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 31. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., June, 1796; (14 items) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 31. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., July, 1796; (21 items) (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 31. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., August, 1796; (20 items) (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 31. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., September, 1796; (20 items) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 31. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., October - November, 1796; (11 items) (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 31. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., October - December, 1796; (13 items) (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 32. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., January, 1797; (18 items) (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 32. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., February, 1797; (18 items) (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 32. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department. (Two letters dated March, 1796.), March, 1797; (18 items) (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 32. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., April, 1797; (15 items) (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 32. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department. (Four items dated April, 1796.), April, 1797; (11 items) (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 32. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., May, 1797; (18 items) (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 32. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., June, 1797; (13 items) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 32. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department. (Four items dated July, 1796.), July, 1797; (16 items) (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 32. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., August, 1796, and August, 1797; (7 items) (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 32. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., September 1 - 19, 1797; (9 items) (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 33. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., September 20 - 30, 1797; (20 items) (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 33. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., October 15, 1797; (15 items) (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 33. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., October 16 - 31, 1797; (15 items) (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 33. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., November, 1797; (13 items) (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 33. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., December 1- 15, 1797; (9 items) (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 33. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., December 16 - 31, 1797; (5 items) (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 34. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., January, 1798; (13 items) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 34. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., February, 1798; (14 items) (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 34. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., March, 1798; (21 items) (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 34. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department. (April and May, 1798 are interfiled.), (22 items) (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 34. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department. (April and May, 1798 are interfiled. One draft dated June 1, 1798.), (24 items) (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 34. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., June 2 - 15, 1798; (17 items) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 34. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., June 16 - 30, 1798; (20 items) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 34. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., July, 1798; (11 items) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 34. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., August 1 - 21, 1798; (11 items) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 35. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., August 22 - 31, 1798; (8 items) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 35. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department; List of American Revenue Cutters employed in the service of the United States--with the names of the Masters and number of Guns., September 1 - 15, 1798; (15 items) (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 35. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department; List of officers commissioned to serve as Mates on board the Revenue Cutters belonging to the several Districts below mentioned., September 16 - 30, 1798; (16 items) (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 35. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., October 1 - 15, 1798; (27 items) (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 35. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., October 16 - November, 1798; (12 items) (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 35. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., Nov. 20 - 30, 1798; (8 items) (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 35. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., December, 1798; (19 items) (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 35. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., August, 1798; (6 items) (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 35. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., September, 1798; (8 items) (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 35. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., October - December, 1798; (7 items) (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 36. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., January, 1799; (13 items) (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 36. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., February, 1799; (8 items) (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 36. Drafts of letters from Treasury Department., March 1 - 15, 1799; (14 items) (Box 19, Folder 17)